(Raj:)or Koothrapemily?
(Howard:)Why is it your last name
and her first name?
(Raj:)Oh, well,
her last name is Sweeney,
(Raj:)and something just didn't seem
right about Koothrapeeney.
(Leonard:)Hey, how'd it go
with human resources?
(Sheldon:)Awful.
Yeah, they're allowing me
to move on from string theory,
(Sheldon:)but they made me
a junior professor
(Sheldon:)and are requiring me
to teach a class.
(Raj:)I don't understand. Why is it
bad that you have to teach?
(Sheldon:)What a stupid question.
(Leonard:)The kids are
gonna love him.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe
I have to waste my time
(Sheldon:)babysitting a bunch
of grad students
(Sheldon:)who probably think dark matter
is what's in their diapers.
(Leonard:)This might not be that bad.
(Leonard:)Uh, you like telling people
they're wrong.
Wrong!
(Sheldon:)Just because I enjoyed that one
doesn't mean I always do.
(Raj:)You enjoy giving
people grades.
(Sheldon:)A valid point,
but unoriginal-- B-minus.